Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1879-1948; 121.0 boxes
  - Subseries 2A: General, 1885-1948; 101.0 boxes
    - The Clarendon Press, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Clark, Anne Hoyt, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Clark, Clarence M, 1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Clark, Evelyn Bigelow [Mrs. J. Francis A. Clark], 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Clark, J. M., 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Clark, John G., 1905-1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Clark, Walter Appleton, 1899; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Clark, Walter L., 1922-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Clark, William A., 1910; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Clark, William F., 1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Clarke, Arthur C., 1928-1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Clarke, C. M., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Clarke, H. A., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Clarke, Issac H., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Clarke, Elizabeth [Mrs. J. O. Clarke], 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Clarke, S. Purdon, 1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Clarke, Thomas B., 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Clausen, Hary M., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Clay, Alfred G., 1926; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Clement, E. H., 1919-1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Clements, Gabrielle D., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Cleveland, Grover, 1887-1900; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Clothier, Issac, 1895-1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Clotheir, Morris, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Clotheir, Robert C., 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - The Clover Club of Philadelphia, 1903; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - "The Club", 1886-1916; 2.0 folders (Folder 40-41)
    - Coal Commission, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Coal Crisis, 1917-1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Coates, Alice U., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Coates, Edward H., 1891-1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Coates, Florence Earle, 1891-1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Coates, Joseph H., 1904-1909; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Coblentz, Stanton A., 1934-1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Coburn and Newmen Publishing Company, 1882; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Coburn, Charles, 1944-1947; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Cochran, William F., 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Codman, Mrs., 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Coffin, William A., 1895-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Coggins, F. Heath & Company, 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Cohen, Lewis, 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Cohen, Mary M., 1891; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Colby, Frank, 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Colby, Josephine Wood, 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Cole, Alphaeus P., 1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Cole, Charles D. M., 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Cole, Timothy, 1919-1925; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Coleman, Ann, 1945; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Coles, Bertha, 1921-1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 21a)
    - Coles, George, 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Coll, Aloysius, 1904; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1923-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Collegeville Hotel, 1888; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Collins, Alan and Dorothy Collins, 1937-1945; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Collins, Philip S., 1905-1943; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Colonial Commercial Company, 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Colonial National Historical Park, 1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Colony Club, 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Columbia University, 1919-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Columbia Yacht Club, 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Columbian Bronze Corporation, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Colvin, Sidney, 1922-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Comfort, Will Levington, 1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Comitato Pro Italia of the Emergency Aid of Pennsylvania, 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Commerical Trust Company, 1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - The Commission of Fine Arts, 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Comimission on Church Building, 1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Committee of American Authors, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Committee of the Peace Award, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Committee on Battle Markers, 1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, 1940; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Commodores' Association of Naragansett Bay, 1917-1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Communist Party of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Community Arts Association of Sanata Barbara, 1922-1925; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Connecticut Yacht Club, 1913-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Conant, Grace [Mrs. James Bryant Conant], 1936-1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Conklin, Julia S., 1905; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Conlen, William J., 1910-1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Connell, William, 1898-1904; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Conner & Stiles, 1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Conner, J. R., 1946; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Conner, John R., 1918-1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Connolly, James B., 1932; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - [skipped], undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Conrad, Thomas R., 1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Conroy, Harrison, 1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Consolidated Shipbuilding Corporation, 1921-1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - "Conte di Cavour", 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - The Contemporary Club, 1887-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Continental Storage Warcharges, 1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Converse, [P. I.], 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Conwell, Russell H., 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Cook, Allen, 1902; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Cook, Edgar, 1911-1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Cook, Edward B., 1911; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Cook, Joel, 1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Cook, Thomas & Son, 1897; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Cook, W. B., 1909; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Cook, Walter, 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Cooke, James Francis, 1920-1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Cooke, Morris Llewellyn, 1926-1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Cookman, J., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Coolidge, J. R., 1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Coombs, Mrs. M. B., 1902; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Coon, Spencer H., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Cooper, Alice, 1892; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Cooper, Emily, 1887-1941; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Cooper, Eva, 1908; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Cooper, Samuel W., 1886-1905; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Cooper, Thomas A., 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Cope, Anne Francis, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton, 1905-1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Cope, Leila, 1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Cope, Thomas, 1912-1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Cope, Walter, 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Copley Galley, 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Copley Plaza Hotel, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - The Copely Society of Boston, 1905; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Coquelin, M. Constant, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Corbit, A., 1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Corcoran, Rosamond Eustis, 1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Corinthian Yacht Club, 1911-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Corkran, Henrietta, 1908; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Corlazzo, Katherine R., 1919-1932; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Cornelius & Rowland Co., 1896; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Cornfield, William H., 1925; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Cornover, Paul R., 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Corriere d'America, 1931; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Corset Fitting Shirt Maker, 1887-1890; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Corson, Ida, 1893-1902; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Corson, L. H., 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - [Cortaggo], Katherine R., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Cortesi, Salvatore, 1916-1932; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Cortissoz, Royal, 1893-1944; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - The Cosmopolitan Magazine, 1892-1895; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Cotton, Georgia [Mrs. William Cotton], 1919-1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Cotton, William H., 1918-1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Courtney, John J., 1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - [Couther] House, 1886; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - The Convenant Presbyterian Church, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Cox and Stevens, 1912-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Cox, Justice, 1883-1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Cox, Kenyon, 1910-1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Cox, Marion G., 1934; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Cox, Sarah S., 1906; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Coxe, E. A., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Coxe, Maria M., 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Coxe, Robert D., 1894; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Craftex Mills, Inc, 1931; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Craig, John T. & Company, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Crain Pump & Lumber Company, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Cram, Ralph Adams, 1920-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Crandall, Charles Henry, 1898-1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Crane, T. I., 1921-1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Crary, Julia Ogden [Mrs. George W.], 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Crasto, Franklin Purdy, 1930-1934; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Creamer, C. R., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Cresson, Margaret, 1930-1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Creswell, Sarah W., 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Cret, Paul Philippe, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - The Critic, 1885-1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Crocco, A. E., 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Cromwell Studio, 1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Crookes, Elizabeth, 1905-1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Crosby, Raymond M., 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Cross, Edgar G., 1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Cross, Wilbur L., 1912-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Crowder, Walter J., 1910-1911; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Crowell, Benjamin Eakins and Leila Eugenia Lanson Crowell, 1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Crown Publications, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Crowninshield, A. S., 1895; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Crowninshield, Frank, 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Crowninshield, Mary B., 1908; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Crumpton, M. N., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Cummings, J. H., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Cunningham, Elizabeth, 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Cunningham, Mark D., 1884-1887; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Cunnington, Morgon, 1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Current Opinion, 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Currie, Barton W., 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Curry, Joseph H., 1916-1941; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Curry, Marie and Catherine Curry, 1926-1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Curtis, Charles P., 1908; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Curtis, Cyrus H. K., 1904-1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - The Curtis Publishing Company, 1905-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Cushing, Howard G., 1899; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Cyclorama of Gettysburg, 1891; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Cyclone Fence Company, 1927-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - D.C. Humphreys Company, 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - DaCosta, J. Chalmers & Mary B. DeCosta, 1908-1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - DaCosta, John, 1910-1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Dagnan-Bouveret P., 1902; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Dagney, John H., 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Daingerfield, Elliot, 1908-1909; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Dakin, Rodney G., 1934; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Dallas, George M., 1880; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - The Dallas News, 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Dallin, Cyrus Edwin, 1940; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Dalton, Mrs. James Leslie, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Dalzel, John, 1909; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Dalziel, John Sanderson, 1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Damrosch Opera Company, 1896-1897; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Damrosch, Walter, 1915-1940; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Dana, Charles E., 1897-1911; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Dana, Millicent, 1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Danforth, Mr., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Dangleman, G. H., 1916-1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Daniel, Ben, 1883; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Daniel, Todd, 1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Dannat, William Turner, 1898; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Dantzig, Meyer, 1932-1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Darrow, George P., 1922-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - D'Ascenzo, Nicola, 1914-1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Davenport, Ruth, 1941; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Davies Battery & Electric Company, Inc., 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Davinci, Leonardo, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - David, Angile, 1898; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Davis, Anna, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Davis, B., 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Davis, Charles Augustus, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Davis, Charles H., 1893-1931; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Davis, D. H., 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Davis, Elizabeth, 1918-1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Davis, Francis Thomas [Mrs. Charles H. Davis], 1934; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Davis, G. G., 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Davis, Harper, 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Davis, Helen Morris, 1899-1909; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Davis, Horace A., 1896; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Davis, Horace B., 1931; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Davis, Lucien, 1908-1910; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Davis, Oliver Wolcott, 1932-1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Davis, Robert H., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Davis, S. Boyer, 1912-1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Davis, Theo M., 1904; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Davis, William H., 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Dawson, George Walter, 1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Dawson, Miles M., 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Day, Anna Blakiston, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Day, Francis, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Day, Frank Miles, 1892-1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Dayton Electrical Machine Company, 1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Dayton Pump and Manufacturing Company, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Deacon, C. B., 1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Deakyne, William F., 1912-1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Dean, George W., 1926-1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Debevoise-Anderson Company, 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - DeCamp, Joseph and Edith DeCamp, 1908-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - DeCoursey, Emily, 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Deckert, Edward P., 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - The Defenders of Truth Society, 1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - DeForest Brothers, 1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - DeKay, Charles, 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - The DeKosenko Manufacturing Company, 1896-1898; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Delafield, Mrs. Moore, 1941; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Deland, Margaret, 1899-1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Delaney, Adelaide Margaret, 1943-1945; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Delaney, Lillian B., 1905; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Delano and Aldrich, 1918-1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - De LaRoche, Francis, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Delaware and Atlantic Telegraph & Telephone Company, 1905; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Delaware and Raritan Canal Commission, 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western Railroad, 1922-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Delk, Edwin Heyl, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Dell, Richard, 1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Dellenbaugh, Mrs. Frederick S., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - The DeLong Hook and Eye Company, 1900; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - DeMare, Baltzar E. L., 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - DeMare, Daisy [Mrs. Baltzar E. L. DeMare], 1922-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - DeMare, Mary, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Demke, Frank, 1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1918-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Democratic Women's Luncheon Club, 1923-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Denison, Charles L., 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Denny, George Parkman, 1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Denton, E. M., 1915-1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Dercum, Francis X., 1904-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Dernberg, Bernhard, 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Derrick, Paul E., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - DeSchauenesse, Maud M., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - DeSchweinitz, G. E., 1921-1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Desmond Fitzgerald, Inc., 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - DeSoito, Joseph, 1927-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 16a)
    - DeVoll, F. Usher, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Dewey, Charles Melville, 1905-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Dewey, Stoddard, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. [ sic. George M. Dewey], 1944; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Dewing, T. W., 1900; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Dewolf, Halsy, 1940; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Dexter, Charles L., 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - DeZouche, John J. Company Ltd., 1894; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - The Dial, 1892-1900; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Diament, A. L. & Company, 1915-1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - The Diamond Rubber Company, 1910-1911; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Dick, Dorothy, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Dick, Mary [Mrs. Lewis R. Dick], 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - The Dickens Fellowship, 1907-1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Dickey, J. M., 1899; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Dickinson, Sidney E., 1918-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Dickson Car Wheel Company, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Dickson, Samuel, 1897-1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Dictionary of American Biography, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Diehm, William, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Dielman, Fredrick, 1908-1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Dilworth, Norris J., 1919-1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Dinsmore, Charles A., 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - D'Invilliers, Edward V., 1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Dirks, [J.] D., 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - The Disabled American Veterans of the World War, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Dismukes, Maude, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Dix, Eulabie, 1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Dixon, Mrs. George Dallas, 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Dixon, Margaretta S., undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Doble, Charles A., 1912-1913; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Dodd, Mead & Company, 1919-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Dodge, James M., 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Doering Treecraft Company, 1930-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Doherty, J. E. Company, 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Dole, Margaret, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Dole, Nathan H., 1906; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Dolente, Louis, 1928-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Doll & Richards, 1922-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Domestic Engine & Pump Company, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Donaldson, Thomas B., 1922-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Donato, Giuseppe, 1903-1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - Donnell, Henry B., 1901; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Donnelley, R. R. & Sons Company, 1936-1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 60)
    - Donahoe, John P., 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 61)
    - Dooner, Richard T., 1920-1945; 1.0 folder (Folder 62)
    - Dorey, William H., 1896; 1.0 folder (Folder 63)
    - Dorman, Marie, 1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 64)
    - Dorme, Helen H. [Mrs. C. Philip Durmel], 1912; 1.0 folder (Folder 65)
    - [Dornuf], W. J., 1898; 1.0 folder (Folder 66)
    - Doskow, Israel, 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 66a)
    - Doubleday, Page & Company, 1916-1926; 1.0 folder (Folder 67)
    - Dougherty, Daniel, 1923-1933; 1.0 folder (Folder 68)
    - Dougherty, Parke C., 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 69)
    - Doughtety, Paul, 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 70)
    - Doulton, Harriet Dorr, 1914; 1.0 folder (Folder 71)
    - Douty, Nicholas, 1911; 1.0 folder (Folder 72)
    - Dovey, John S., 1892; 1.0 folder (Folder 73)
    - Dowling, Philip, 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 74)
    - Downes, W. H., 1907-1931; 1.0 folder (Folder 75)
    - Doyle, Michael Francis, 1944; 1.0 folder (Folder 76)
    - Drake, Ada Brooke, 1908; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Drake, Charles E., 1914-1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Dreer, Henry A., Inc., 1913-1932; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Drew, Mary, 1905-1906; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Dexel & Company, 1901-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Drexel Institute of Technology, 1895-1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Drinker, Henry S., 1912-1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Drohan, Thomas Wharton, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Drummund, M. H., 1907; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Drury, William H., 1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Duckstein, [Freman] and Caroline Duckstein, 1898-1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Duer, Caroline, 1904; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Duffy, James O., 1913-1930; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Dufuer, Edward, 1935; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Duhring, H. Louis, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Dull, John J., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Dumond, Frank V., 1905-1932; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Dumpling Wharf, 1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Dunbar, Paul Lawrence, 1901-1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Duncan, G. A., 1921-1927; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Duncan, J., 1918; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Duncan, J. G., 1919-1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Duncannon Iron Company, 1908; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - The Dunes Club, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Dunham Sales Company, Inc., 1936; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Dunlap, William A., 1919-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Dupont Family, 1931-1940; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Durant, Lucy S., 1929; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Durham, Constance Mackenzie, 1920-1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Dutee, Wilcox Flint, Inc., 1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Dutton, William Dalliba, 1890-1896; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Dyer, H. Anthony, 1928; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Dyer, Nancy, 1923-1943; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Dykstra, Marten, 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - E. P. Duton & Company, Inc., 1922-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Eakins, Thomas, 1909-1945; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Earle, George, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Earle, Laura H., 1899; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Earth, 1937; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Eastman Kodak Company, 1915; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Easton, C. H., 1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Easton, R. J. & Son, 1915-1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Economic Club of Philadelphia, 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Eddy, Arthur J., 1896-1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Eddy, Jerome O., 1913-1920; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Edelheim, Carl, 1899; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Edison, Charles, 1943; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Edmonds, Franklin S., 1906-1944; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Edmonds, George W., 1923-1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Edmunds, Albert J., 1913-1938; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Edward MacDowell Association, 1925-1942; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Edwards, Mrs. David G., 1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Edwards, Duncan, 1924; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Edwards, George Wharton, 1911-1939; 2.0 folders (Folder 20-21)
    - Edwards, Louise Betts, 1902-1910; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Edwin Forest Home, 1922-1939; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Egan, M. G., 1919; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Egan, Maurice Francis, 1899-1923; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - The Ehrich Galleries, 1912-1921; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Eitel, Edward H., 1916; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Eizo Kondo, 1917; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Elder, Louise, 1917-1922; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)